# Can get question data API from https://opentdb.com/

question_data = [
    {"category": "General Knowledge",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "'Typewriter'; is the longest word that can be typed using only the first row on a QWERTY keyboard.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },
    {"category": "General Knowledge",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Coca-Cola's original colour was green.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge",
     "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The US emergency hotline is 911 because of the September 11th terrorist attacks.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
     },
    {"category": "General Knowledge",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The vapor produced by e-cigarettes is actually water.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
     },
    {"category": "General Knowledge",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The sum of all the numbers on a roulette wheel is 666.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },
    {"category": "General Knowledge",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Furby was released in 1998.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },
    {"category": "General Knowledge",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "There are 86400 seconds in a day.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },
    {"category": "General Knowledge",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The word &quot;news&quot; originates from the first letters of the 4 main directions on a compass (North, East, West, South).",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
     },
    {"category": "General Knowledge",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "An eggplant is a vegetable.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
     },
    {"category": "General Knowledge",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The bikini is named after the 'Bikini Atoll', an island where the United States conducted tests on atomic bombs.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     }
    ]
